https://campnashobaday.com/site-policy/

Site Policy
Site Policy:
Camp Nashoba® Day is a registered trademark. All rights reserved. When you visit www.campnashobaday.com, we recognize your domain name so that we can analyze the traffic flow to our site, but we do not collect your email address unless you specifically ask us to do so by filling out an Information Request or Alumni Registry. Our traffic logs are used for internal review only and are discarded regularly. If you fill out our Information Request or Alumni Registry page, we retain the information you provide us so that we can send you periodic information about our camp. We do not as a matter of policy sell that information to other businesses or organizations. If at any time you would like to be deleted from our email mailing list, please let us know. Camp Nashoba Day is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site. We collect information in several ways from different parts of our web site. Some personal information is gathered when you complete the Information Request Form. We ask for your name, email address, child’s age and grade, city, state, zip code, and phone number. We also collect personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you email us about camp availability or job availability. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Finally, we measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of our web site you have visited, and your visiting patterns. We use this information to help us identify which areas of our site needs to be expanded or enhanced. Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to be able to improve our communication with you as a potential or existing camper, alumni or staff. We also use this information to learn more about what information you need to make your visit to our web site productive, more informative and/or entertaining. When you are on our site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Camp Nashoba Day alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. For example, some services are accessible to other members and not just the staff at Camp Nashoba Day. As a general rule, we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information. We may, from time to time, send you email regarding our camp and related services. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you receive an email message from us. Camp Nashoba Day does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. We comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. When a child under age 13 attempts to register with us, we ask that they have a parent or guardian register on their behalf. This is to ensure that the parent or guardian consents to the use of personally identifying information from that child. If a parent wishes to refuse to permit further collection or use of their child’s information, that parent can send an email to us to request deletion of their child’s account. Under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, no web site operator is permitted to require a child under the age of 13 to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity as a condition of participation. We abide by this requirement. We do not share personally identifying information about users who are under the age of 13 with business partners or other third parties. Any questions about this policy statement may be emailed to campashoba@gmail.com or you may write to us at our office using the address at the bottom of each page.
Winter 140 Nashoba Road
Littleton, Mass. 01460
Ph: 978.486.8088
Summer
140 Nashoba Road
Littleton, Mass. 01460
Ph: 978.486.8088
Winter
© 2014 Camp Nashoba™ Day. All rights reserved. Sitemap. Website by 829 Studios.
